Guide to the Paul LeBlanc Papers, 1967-1998 AIS.1974.17
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Research, IV.
  - Articles on Politics and Political Theory, 1990-1995 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Article about Rosa Luxemburg (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Articles about the World Congress of the Fourth International (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Communist and Socialist Publications and Correspondence, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Communist and Socialist Papers and Notes by Paul LeBlanc (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Articles about Czechoslovakia (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Articles about Eastern Europe (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Articles on European Labor History (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Articles about France (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Articles about Germany and Socialism (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Articles on Central America and Anti-Intervention (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Articles about Cuba (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Articles on Latin America (Box 25, Folder 8-10)
  - Articles on Latin America (Nicaragua) and Socialism/Political Movements, 1984-1986 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Articles on Latin America (Nicaragua) and Socialism/Political Movements, 1986-1988 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Articles on Latin America (Nicaragua) and Socialism/Political Movements, 1933 & 1983-1987 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Articles about Russia and Socialism/Labor (Box 25, Folder 14-15)
  - Articles about U.S. Marxists and Leftists (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Articles about U.S. Politics and Society (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Articles about the U.S. "Right" (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Articles about the U.S.A. and Socialism (Box 25, Folder 19-20)
  - Articles on Leninism (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Articles on Socialism and Communism (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Articles on Socialism and Labor (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Articles on Socialism and Marxism (Box 25, Folder 24-26)
  - "Anarchy and Anarchists" (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - "After the Wall, A New Socialism?" from the Nation by Daniel Singer, December 1989 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - "An Introduction to Marxist Economics" and "Maoism and Revolution" (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - "To Build a New World" (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - "Building a Socialist Movement in the U.S." (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - "The Challenge of Spoleto" from the New York Times, June 1987 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - "Requiem for a Steel Town" from the New York Times, September 5, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - "Did Trotsky Oppose Entering the Guomindang 'From the First'?" by Alexander Pantsov and Gregor Benton (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - "Documentation on the Expulsion of Malik Miah from the Socialist Workers Party" (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - "Economic Determinants of Perestroika" (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - "Formation of the Labor Party" (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - "From Marxism to Conservatism" by James Burnham, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - "Globalisation mondiale contre U.E.M.?" by Claude Gabriel, August 1967 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - "Industrial Development and Strategies in Revolutionary Nicaragua" (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - "Leon Trotsky: Life and Ideas" (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - "Lessons from the Past and Our Choice of Direction" by Danny Rubin (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - "Marx and the Dictatorship of the Proletariat" (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - "The May Student Strike" by Tony Fels (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - "The Significance of the State Department" May 2nd Committee (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Men's Feminism: August Bebel and the German Socialist Movement (Loose Book), 1995 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - "The Marxist Tradition" (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - "Modern Politics" by CLR James, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - "The Myth of Lenin's 'Concept of the Party' of What They Did to..." (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - "The Nicaraguan Revolution" by Gary Prevost, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - "On the Nature of the Chinese Bureaucracy Regime", 1990 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - "Pensiero E Azione Politica Di Lev Trockij" (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - "Perspectives for Democracy and Socialism in the 1990s" Conference (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - "Proposal for Selling Intervention: Domestic Propaganda and U.S. Foreign Policy" by Michael Livington, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - "The Road to Power", 1909 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - "Socialism and Spirituality" from the Monthly Review Press by Paul Buhle and Thomas Fiehrer, November 1985 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - "Theses on North American Continental Integration and the World Market" by Francoise M., 1991 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - "Trade and Aid in Latin American-CMEA Relations: The Cases of Peru and Nicaragua" by Ruben Berrios (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - "Why Be a Marxist?" by Ernest Mandel (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Zen-Marxism: Chapter Six by Mitchel Cohen, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - "Victor Serge and the N.Y. Anti-Stalinist Left" (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - Reports by Carol McAllister, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - Reports by Carl Skoglund (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - Reports by Joel Hodroff (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - Reports by John Kovach and Karen Buchholz (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - Report by L.H. Haimson (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - Readings by M. Lowy (Box 26, Folder 41)
  - Readings on Alexander Bogdanov, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 42)
  - Papers on China and Trotskyism & Bolshevism (Box 26, Folder 43)
  - Reports on Victor Serge (Box 26, Folder 44)
  - Readings for a Conference (Box 26, Folder 45)
  - Abortion Rights, 1990-1991 (Box 26, Folder 46)
  - African Americans and Politics (Box 26, Folder 47)
  - Airport (Box 26, Folder 48)
  - Anti-NAFTA Material (Box 26, Folder 49)
  - APA, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 50)
  - Archbishop Romero Day of Reflection (Box 26, Folder 51)
  - Books and Publications Information, 1987-1992 (Box 26, Folder 52)
  - Book Shop Notes (Box 26, Folder 53)
  - Book Catalogs (Box 26, Folder 54)
  - Boundaries Training - United Methodists of Western Pennsylvania, May 22-25, 1996 (Box 26, Item 1)
  - "Breast Cancer: You Are Your Best Defense" (Box 26, Item 2)
  - "Campaign to Win" Against Levi Strauss Information, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 55)
  - Canadian Publications (Box 26, Folder 56)
  - "The Carl Beck Papers in Russian and East European Studies" (Box 26, Item 3-4)
  - Caterair in Flight Letter (Box 26, Folder 57)
  - Central America (Box 27, Folder 1-5)
  - Center on Budget and Policy Priorities (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - China (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - China and "Crisis of Maoism" Reports, 1981-1996 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - China and Hong Kong (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Community Advisory Boards (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Critiques of the Socialist Workers Party, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Cuba (Box 27, Folder 12-14)
  - Daniel Libreros Case, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Debate on Afghanistan, 1981 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - "Development of Marxism" Diagram (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Eastern Europe (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - El Salvador, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Ernest Mandel (Box 27, Folder 20-21)
  - "Exploring Health Careers" Report (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Facing the Challenge: Steelworkers Speak Out (Box 27, Item 1)
  - Fair Trade, 1991-1992 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Fidel Castro on Chile Review (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Financial Record Keeping Handbook, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Fisher Scientific Reports and Response (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Foreign Publications (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - Frank Lovell (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - Germany and Socialist & Labor, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - The Great Steel Strike (Box 27, Item 2)
  - Indonesia (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Inequalities in Minnesota Booklets by Doug Mann (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - International Socialist (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - International Work (Box 27, Folder 33-34)
  - Internationalism and Imperialism, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - IPAN (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - Iran - Workers (Box 27, Folder 37)
  - Israel and the Middle East (Alternative Information Center), 1989 (Box 27, Folder 38)
  - Japan (Box 27, Folder 39)
  - Karl Marx Centenary Conference Program Book (Box 27, Folder 40)
  - Labor Education (Box 27, Folder 41)
  - Labor Lectures, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 42)
  - Labor Unions and Labor Party Writings, 1952-1991 (Box 27, Folder 43)
  - Labor's Corner Program Listing (Box 27, Folder 44)
  - Lamberists (Box 27, Folder 45)
  - Latin America and Socialism (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Lenin, Trotsky and the Bureaucratizing of the Soviet State (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Leninist Party (Box 28, Folder 3-4)
  - Leninism (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Lithuania (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - "Making a Difference for Non-Profits: 1997 Annual Report" (Box 28, Item 1)
  - Maria's Story (Box 28, Folder 7-8)
  - Martin Luther King Jr. and Anti-Racism (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Marxism Now: Traditions and Difference Conference, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Marxism (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - McBorderland U.S.A: The Maquiladora Industry and the Selling of El Paso Texas and Ciudad Juarez Mexico by Jim Dougherty, 1990 (Box 28, Item 2)
  - Mexico (Box 28, Folder 12-13)
  - Middle East (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous Meeting Minutes and Reports (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous Publishing and Book Related Materials (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Nicaragua, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Labor Movements in Nicaragua (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Witness for Peace Publications on Nicaragua, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Party Struggle: The Blurring of Marxism (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Photocopies of Newspapers from the Late 1800s (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Physicians for a National Health Program, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Pro-Choice Rallies, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Racism (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Revolutionary Studies/Humanities Press (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - "The Russian Revolution" Compiled by Anthony Cash (Box 28, Item 3)
  - Russian Marxism, Bolshevism and Leninism (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Reverend Willis Ludlow (Box 28, Folder 27-28)
  - Pamphlets on Socialism (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Socialist Meetings and Classes (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - South Africa (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - South African Apartheid (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Sri Lanka (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - "Study Guide for Sociology 846: The Vietnam War and Intervention" (Box 28, Item 4)
  - Tamiment (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - Tribunal Internacional Contra La Deuda, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - Tunisia, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - U.S. and Socialism (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - The U.S. and the Gulf War (Box 28, Folder 38)
  - Union (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - Union Advocate Newspaper (Box 28, Item 5)
  - University of Michigan, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 40)
  - Volunteer Professionals Serving Non-Profits (Box 28, Item 6)
  - Video Library (Box 28, Folder 41)
  - Writings on Women's Liberation (Box 28, Folder 42)
  - Women and Labor (Box 28, Folder 43)
  - Workers Unions at the University of Pittsburgh, 1972-1973 (Box 28, Folder 44)
  - Youngstown State University (Box 28, Item 7-8)
  - Zionism (Box 28, Folder 45)
- Personal, V.
  This series contains personal material belonging to LeBlanc such as his articles, notebooks, notes and correspondence. Also found in this series are copies of articles or manuscripts that were sent to LeBlanc by his peers for his review and opinion.
  - "The Challenge of the Nicaraguan Revolution" (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - "Luxembourg and Lenin on Revolutionary Organization" (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - "Reflections on the Fourth International Tendency" (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Rosa Luxemburg (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - "Pioneers of American Socialism" (Box 29, Folder 5-6)
  - "The Stalin Collection" (Box 29, Folder 7-8)
  - Workers and Revolution by Paul LeBlanc (Box 29, Folder 9-16)
  - "Memories of SDS, Lessons for the Future" (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - "Vanguards in the U.S." (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - "Negative and Positive Lessons from the Bolshevik Experience" (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - "American History" (Box 29, Item 1)
  - "'Castroism' and the Marxist Tradition" (Box 29, Item 2)
  - "Literature" (Box 29, Item 3)
  - "Philosophy" (Box 29, Item 4)
  - Bolshevik Theory (Box 29, Item 5)
  - "A Short History of the U.S. Working Class" (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Permanent Revolution in Nicaragua (Box 30, Item 1-2)
  - Solidarity (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - "Revolutionary Socialists Unify" by Paul LeBlanc, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - "Left Wing Science Fiction: Future Perfect" by Paul LeBlanc (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - "The Century of Hannah Arendt and CLR James" by Paul LeBlanc (Box 30, Folder 5-6)
  - "Unfolding Marxism" (Box 30, Folder 7-8)
  - "A Short History of the U.S. Working Class" (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - "From Revolutionary Intellectual to Conservative Master Thinker" by Paul LeBlanc (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - "The Tragedy of American Communism" by Paul LeBlanc, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - "From Marxism to Conservatism" by Paul LeBlanc (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - "The Bolshevik Revolution Did Not Create a..." and "The Leninist Party" by Paul LeBlanc (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - "The Aftermath of the Bolshevik Revolution" by Paul LeBlanc (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - In Defense of American Trotskyism by Paul LeBlanc (Box 30, Folder 15-16)
  - "Dialectics of the Jackson Campaign" by Paul LeBlanc (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - "Unfolding Marxism: A Way of Seeing, A Guide to Action" by Paul LeBlanc (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - A Unbound Book by Paul LeBlanc (Box 30, Folder 19-20)
  - Papers by Paul LeBlanc (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Carlow College (Box 30, Item 3-4)
  - Articles by Paul LeBlanc (Box 30, Folder 22-23)
  - Articles by Paul LeBlanc and Curriculum Vitae (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Articles and Correspondence by Paul LeBlanc (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Articles on Russia and Nicaragua by Paul LeBlanc (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Articles by Paul LeBlanc (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Education (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Publications, 1968-1975 (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - Personal Poems (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - Various Papers and Articles by Paul LeBlanc (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - Memo on Dobbs Manuscript (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - Articles by Paul LeBlanc (Box 30, Folder 33-34)
  - Pre-Convention Discussion, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - Articles about Labor by Paul LeBlanc (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - "Does Re-Evaluation Counseling Stand on the Shoulders of Marxism? The Role of Quality of Life Issues in the Revolutionary Transformation of Society" by Joel Hodroff (Box 30, Folder 37)
  - "Geography: How it Played a Role in the Birth and Death of the Steel Industry in Pittsburgh" (Box 30, Folder 38)
  - Serge and Trotsky (Box 30, Folder 39)
  - "The Best of What We Are..." by J. Brentlinger (Box 30, Folder 40)
  - Critical Notes on Perlman (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Thorstein Veblen Book (Box 31, Folder 2-3)
  - "Algebra of Revolution" (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Bruce Nelson (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - George Novack (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - "The Best of What We Are..." by J. Brentlinger (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Bruce Levine (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - "Cuban Labour and the Cold War" (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Hubert Perrier (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Hal Draper - Haberkern (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Books Proposals Received (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Agenda of Prospects and Tasks (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Les Evans (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Papers by Friends (Box 31, Folder 15-16)
  - Weissman/Serge (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Marxism and the Jacobin Communist Tradition, 1970 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - The Meaning of World War II by Ernest Mandel (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - David Mandel (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - "The Best of What We Are" by John Brentlinger (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - CLR Jones (Box 32, Folder 3-5)
  - Frank Lovell and S.W.P. Books, 1991-1992 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Marxist Theory (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Livio Maitan (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - "Women's Autobiographies" and "The Catalan Revolution" (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Alan Wald (Box 32, Folder 10-12)
  - International Trotskyism by Robert Alexander, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Lowy Essays (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Ernest Mandel (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Autobiographical and Other Materials of Dan Rosenshine (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Chicago Project (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Albert Parsons (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Articles and Notes (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Notes (Box 32, Folder 20-21)
  - Notes and Correspondence (Box 32, Folder 22-25)
  - Notes on Lenin (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Notes on Convention of July 22-24, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - Party Struggle - November 1981 Plenum (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Party Struggle - February-March 1982 Plenum (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Party Struggle - August 1982 Plenum (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Party Struggle - Poland (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Party Struggle - Cuba (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Party Struggle - Lenin Classes in Pittsburgh (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Pittsburgh Branch Struggle (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Pre-Convention Discussion, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Pierre Rousset (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Socialist Workers Party Book Materials (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Paul Buhle (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Lenin Book (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Notebook of Hand-Written Notes (Box 33, Item 1-2)
  - Notes (Box 33, Folder 13-14)
  - Reports by Paul LeBlanc (Box 33, Folder 15-16)
  - U.S. History (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Revolutionary Studies (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Nicaragua (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Mailing List (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Notes (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous Notes and Correspondence (Box 33, Item 3)
  - Rosa Luxemburg (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Personal Writing (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Dick Hunt (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Paul Siegel (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Sewickley Country Inn and Conference Center, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence (Box 33, Folder 28-30)
  - Wohl Forth (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - Cannon Letters (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - George Shriver (Box 33, Folder 33)
  - Dennis Brutus (Box 33, Folder 34)
  - Buhle (Box 33, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence between Paul LeBlanc and P. Rousset (Box 33, Folder 36)
  - Molly Rush (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Paul Sweezy and Harry Magdoff (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence and Notes (Box 34, Item 1)
  - Lenin Book Correspondence (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Lowy - Essays (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - U.S.S.R./Vogt-Downey (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Traverso (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Morris Slavin (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Sweden (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Rousset (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Alan Wald (Box 34, Folder 10-11)
  - Lou Patras (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Janet Melvin (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Elenor Mart (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence with Ernest Mandel (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence between Paul LeBlanc and Steve, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence/Ashfield (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Stephanie Coontz Correspondence (Box 34, Folder 18-19)
  - Dave Montgomery (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Phil Foner (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Marilyn Vogt (Box 34, Folder 22-23)
  - Steve Nelson (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Details (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Brenner (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence with David Finkel (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Dick Oestreicher (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - Workshop Speakers, Resource Persons and Convenors (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - Bills Paid to LeBlanc (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - Finances (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - Bills Unpaid to LeBlanc (Box 34, Folder 32)
  - Bills and Finances (Box 34, Folder 33-34)
  - LeBlanc's Trial (Box 34, Folder 35)
  - Notebooks (Box 34, Folder 36)
  - Slippery Rock University (Box 34, Folder 37)
  - Personal - Academic and Job (Box 34, Folder 38)
  - Employment (Box 34, Folder 39)
  - Courses Taken (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - University of Pittsburgh (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Computer Prep (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Notes (Box 35, Item 1)
  - Class Materials of Paul LeBlanc (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Class Lectures and Evaluations of Paul LeBlanc, 1990-1991 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Others' Version of History 741 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - History 741 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - History 741 (Box 35, Item 2)
  - History 741 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - History 741 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Reading Lists and Fellowships (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Committee in Solidarity with the People of El Salvador, June 1991 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Paul LeBlanc Curriculum Vitae (Box 35, Folder 12)